<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
    <name>Vanilla Chemfuel Expanded - Odyssey Patch</name>
    <author>Bulldog</author>
    <packageId>Bulldog.VanillaChemfuelExpandedOdysseyPatch</packageId>
    <description>A quick and dirty patch to integrate the gravship engine and vanilla chemfuel tanks into the Vanilla Chemfuel Expanded pipe network. 
        
This patch turns vanilla chemfuel tanks into VCE enabled pipe network storage. The gravengine also has to be connected to the pipe network to actually use the chemfuel in it, and it won't glow if it doesn't have access to chemfuel (which totally wasn't an unintended side effect, I'm taking the credit).
This does also mean that you can now use VCE chemfuel tanks, which are much larger than vanilla tanks, to store fuel for your engine. I decided to leave that unchanged, so you can decide for yourself whether or not you want to use them.

As a side effect of this, the gravship at the start of the Odyssey scenario will have empty chemfuel tanks, but I have modified the scenario to provide the player with the same amount of chemfuel in item form, as well as a VCE chemfuel drain to fill the tanks with. Just be aware that you need to fill the tanks to take off initially.

I was able to make sure that this is safe to add to an existing save. Your vanilla chemfuel tanks should have the same amount of fuel they had before this mod was added. I tested this on a few saves of mine, and it seemed to work well, but if you encounter issues, you can unload the chemfuel tanks manually, save, and only then add the mod.
        
This will probably get taken down if/when VCE updates.
    </description>
    <supportedVersions>
        <li>1.6</li>
    </supportedVersions>
    <modDependencies>
        <li>
            <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
            <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
            <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
        </li>
        <li>
            <packageId>VanillaExpanded.VChemfuelE</packageId>
            <displayName>Vanilla Chemfuel Expanded</displayName>
            <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2792917473</steamWorkshopUrl>
        </li>
    </modDependencies> 
</ModMetaData>